Finding Aid for the Edwin Sheffield Gleaves Papers
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
Edwin Sheffield Gleaves Papers
undated
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
MSS.0170
23.75 linear feet
- PERSONAL CORRESPONDENCE (U.S.), 1958 - 1986
  - 1958-1963 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - incoming, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - outgoing, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - incoming, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - outgoing, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - incoming, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - outgoing, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - University of Washington, 1965-1967 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - University of Houston, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - incoming, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - outgoing, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Business (incoming), 1967 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Business (outgoing), 1967 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - 1968 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - 1969 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - 1970 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Peabody, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Peabody, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Library School, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - General, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - General, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - 1972 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Tennessee Library Association, 1972-73 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - 1973 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - 1974 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - 1975 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - 1976 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - 1977-78 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - 1979 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - 1980 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - 1981 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - 1982 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - 1983 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - 1984 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - 1985 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - 1986 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Frances Neel Cheney – Edwin S. Gleaves (Box 1, Folder 37)
- PERSONAL CORRESPONDENCE (LATIN AMERICA), 1974-1987
  - Correspondence -- ELB (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence -- Argentina (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence -- Colombia, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence -- Kozano -- Rivera (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence -- Colombia, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence -- Colombia, 1976-1980 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence -- Costa Rica, University of (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence -- Costa Rica, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence -- Ecuador, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence -- Mexico-Conacyt, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence -- Mexico-Conacyt, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence -- Mexico, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence -- Mexico, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence -- Mexico, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Mexico -- Microforms Workshop Oct, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence -- Mexico, 1979-1980 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence -- Mexico -- Universidad de Guanajuato, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence -- Mexico -- Universidad de Guanajuato, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence -- Mexico -- Universidad de Guanajuato, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence -- Mexico -- Universidad de Guanajuato, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence -- Mexico, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Correspondence -- Paraguay, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Correspondence -- Venezuela (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Fulbright Grant, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Fulbright Grant, 1986-1987 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Organization of American States (Box 2, Folder 26)
- LS 221/LIS 2210, SELECTION / COLLECTION DEVELOPMENT (1)
  - LS 221 -- Book Selection (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - LS 221 -- Course of Study (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - LIS 2210 -- Class Calendar for Summer Session, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - LS 221 -- Schedule of Field Trips and Visiting Speeches (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - LIS 2210 -- Notable Books, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - LS 221 -- Class Calendar (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - LIS 2210 -- Unit 4; The Selector and Book Selection Aids; Related Readings (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - LIS 2210 -- Unit 5; Selection of Editions and Translations: Related Readings (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - LIS 2210 -- Unit 6; Selection of Nonbook Materials; Related Readings (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - LIS 2210 -- Unit 7; Variations by Type of Library: Related Readings (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - LIS 2210 -- Unit 8; Acquisitions: Related Readings (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - LIS 2210 -- Sample Record Labels and Prices (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - LS 221 -- Microformulations (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - LIS 2210 -- Evaluative Criteria in the Selection of Sound Recordings (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - LIS 2210 -- Library Collection Development -- Course of Study, Spring, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - LIS 2210 -- Schedule of Class Meetings, Summer, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - LIS 2210 -- Library Collection Development -- Basic Bibliography, Spring, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - LIS 2210 -- Library Collection Development -- Related Readings, Spring, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - LIS 2210 -- Unit 1; The Library and Its Community: Related Readings (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - LIS 2210 -- Unit 2; The Publishing Trade: Related Readings (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - LIS 2210 -- Unit 3; Principles and Policies for Materials Selection: Related Readings (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - LIS 2210 -- Review of Recorded Classical Music, by Arthur Cohn (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - LIS 2210 -- A Musical Survey (ESG) (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - LIS 2210 -- Bibliographic Control of Software -- Class Materials (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - LIS 2210 -- Who Wrote What: A Non-literary Quiz (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - LIS 2210 -- Who Wrote What: A Non-literary Quiz (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - LIS 2210 -- Unit 9; Resource Sharing: Related Readings (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - LIS 2210 -- Unit 10; Collection Evaluation: Related Readings (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - LIS 2210 -- Unit 11; Weeding, Storage, and Preservation: Related Readings (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - LIS 2210 -- Unit 12; Censorship and Selection: Related Readings (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - LIS 2210 -- Bibliography (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - LS 221 -- Assignments (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - LIS 2210 -- Library Collection Development -- Assignments (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - LIS 2210/3070 -- Editions and Translations: Some Questions (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - LS 221 -- Problem Books: Case Study and Report (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - LIS 2210 -- Annotation I (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - LS 221 -- Annotation of Reviews (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - LS 221 -- Notable Materials Project (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - LIS 2210 -- Book Review (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - LIS 2210 -- Class Calendar, 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - LIS 2210 -- Annotation II (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - LIS 2210 -- Special Materials -- for Special People (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - LIS 2210 --Developing A Materials Selection Policy (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - LIS 2210 -- Library Collection Development -- The Basic Repertoire (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - LS 221 -- Here Comes the Sun: Libraries and Solar Energy Information Transfer (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - LS 221 -- Ahora Conoces -- Que? (Box 3, Folder 46)
  - LS 221 -- Oral Book Reviews (Box 3, Folder 47)
  - LS 221 -- Music (Box 3, Folder 48)
  - LIS 2210 -- “Introductory Notes to Classical Music: A Personal Selection” (ESG) (Box 3, Folder 49)
  - LIS 2210 -- “Classical Music: A Personal Selection” (ESG) (Box 3, Folder 50)
  - LIS 2210 -- “Tools for the Selection of Classical Music Recordings” (Box 3, Folder 51)
  - LIS 2210 -- Music “Best Recordings of the Past Twenty Years” (Stereo Review) (Box 3, Folder 52)
  - LS 221 -- Classical Music Recordings: Not the Best (Box 3, Folder 53)
  - LIS 2210 -- The Basic Repertoire, Unit 6 (Box 3, Folder 54)
  - LIS 2210 -- A Personal Basic Repertoire (Box 3, Folder 55)
  - LIS 2210 -- The Basic Repertoire (Box 3, Folder 56)
  - LIS 2210 -- Music -- Catalogers (Box 3, Folder 57)
  - LIS 2210 -- Recommended Lists of Music (Box 3, Folder 58)
  - LS 221 -- Hoffmann, “A Basic Recorded Sound Collection” (Box 3, Folder 59)
  - LS 221 -- A Recommended Basic Repertoire (Box 3, Folder 60)
  - LIS 2210 -- The Basic Repertoire, Unit 6 -- Original (Box 3, Folder 61)
  - LS 221 -- The Basic Repertoire (Box 3, Folder 62)
  - LS 221 - Recordings (Box 3, Folder 63)
  - LIS 2210 -- Music -- Performance Series (Box 3, Folder 64)
  - LS 221 -- Schwann’s Most Frequently Recorded Classical Performers (Box 3, Folder 65)
  - LS 221 -- Music -- “The $150 Record Collection” (Box 3, Folder 66)
  - LIS 2210 -- “The Most Recorded Symphonies” (Box 3, Folder 67)
  - LIS 2210 -- Music -- Order Forms (Box 3, Folder 68)
  - LS 221 -- Schwann’s “Basic Record Library” (Box 3, Folder 69)
  - LS 221 -- The Best Classical Recording of, 1976 and 1977 (Box 3, Folder 70)
  - LS 221 -- A New Musical Joke? An Objection to an Objection (Box 3, Folder 71)
  - LS 221 -- Music -- “Best Recordings of the Past Twenty Years” (Stereo Review) (Box 3, Folder 72)
  - LS 221 -- The Basic Repertoire, 1973-1974 (Box 3, Folder 73)
  - LS 221 -- The Basic Repertoire, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 74)
  - LS 221 -- Tools of the Trade “Problem Sheet” (Box 3, Folder 75)
  - LS 221 -- “Glossary of Library Terms” (ALA) (Box 3, Folder 76)
- LS 221/LIS 2210, SELECTION / COLLECTION DEVELOPMENT (2)
  - LIS 2210 -- Supreme Court -- Decision on New York School Board (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - LIS 2210 -- Reading on Intellectual Freedom (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Tennessee Department of Education Committee on HJR 341 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - LS 221 -- Assignments -- The Seven Minutes (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - LS 221 -- Censorship -- “It Can Happen Here: A Censorship Role Play” (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - LS 221 -- Censorship -- “The Freedom to Read” (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - LS 221 -- Censorship -- The Test of Civilization (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - LS 221 -- Questionable Books, Problem Books (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - LS 221 -- Censorship (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - LIS 2210 -- Freedom to Read, Foundation News (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - LIS 2210 -- ALA Office for Intellectual Freedom (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - LS 221 -- Library Cooperation (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - LIS 2210 -- Approved Plans (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - LS 221 -- Standards for University Libraries, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - LS 221 -- Community Junior College Libraries, Standards, etc. (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - LIS 2210 -- Standards for College Libraries, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - LIS 2210 -- “A Method for Quantitatively Evaluating a University Library Collection (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - LIS 2210 -- Standards -- Academic Libraries (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - LS 221 -- Guidelines for Two-Year College Learning Resources Programs (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - LIS 2210 -- Usage Count for Periodicals, Lambuth College (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - LIS 2210 -- A Droll Role Play: A Public Encounter over a Controversial Book (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - LS 221 -- A Droll Role Play, (Spring and Summer 1979) (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - LS 221 -- Portraits of the Artists (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - LIS 2210 -- Standards for College Libraries, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - LIS 2210 -- “Evaluating Collections by Their Use” (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - LS 221 -- Serials (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - LS 221 -- Book Selection -- Standards, Formulae, Criteria, etc. (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - LIS 2210 -- Collection Development Policies (T.R.) (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - LS 221 -- The Most Censored Materials in the U. S. (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - The Nature of Faith by the Use of Books (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - LIS 2210 -- NICEM Indexes (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - LS 221 -- Standards for College Libraries (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - LS 221 -- Standing Order Plans (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - LS 322 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - LS 322 -- Introduction (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - LS 322 -- Bibliography of Humanities, (Summer 1980) (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - LS 322 -- Humanities RQ (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - LS 322 -- Course of Study and Assignments, (Summer 1980) (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - LS 322 -- Pathfinder Project (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - LS 322 -- Variations on Religious Themes (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - LS 322 -- Memo on Assignment Preference (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - LS 322 -- Bibliography of Humanities -- Philosophy: Questions for Discussion (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - LS 322 -- Music Writings and Recordings (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - LS 322 -- Art Assignment (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - LS 322 -- Visual Arts (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - LS 322 -- A Basic Literary Bibliography (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - LS 322 -- Musical Heritage Society (Box 4, Folder 47)
  - LS 322 -- Language and Literature (Box 4, Folder 48)
  - LS 307/322 -- “English Literature: Selected Reference Sources” (Box 4, Folder 49)
  - LS 307/322 -- “American Literature: All Periods” (SIU Guide) (Box 4, Folder 50)
  - LS 322 -- Performing Arts (Box 4, Folder 51)
  - LS 322 -- The Computer and the Humanities (Box 4, Folder 52)
  - LS 502a (Peabody) (Box 4, Folder 53)
- LS 320/LIS 3200, MICROGRAPHICS
  - LS 320 -- Course of Study (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - LIS 3200 -- Micrographics in Libraries -- Course of Study (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - LIS 3200 -- Course of Study, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - LIS 3200 -- Course of Study, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - NMA, Introduction to Micrographics (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - LS 320 -- Bibliography (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - LS 3200 -- Learning Activities and Assignments (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - LS 320 -- Supplementary Readings (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - LS 320 -- Assignments: Learning Activities (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - LS 320 -- Class Calendar (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - LS 320 -- Microfiche or Roll Film? (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - LIS 3200 -- Gleaves, Edwin S. “A Microform Program for Duckworth Libraries” (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - LIS 3200 -- Reference Sources (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Jonathan Livingston Librarian (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - LS 320 -- Microfiche Readers for Libraries (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - LS 320 -- Benefits of the Serials in Microform (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - A New Library -- Without a New Building (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - LIS 3200 -- University Microfilms International (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - LS 320 -- “A New Library -- Without a New Building” (floor plan) (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - LS 320 -- User Environment and Attitudes in an Academic Microform Center (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - LIS 3200 -- Non-silver Microforms in a Working Environment (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - IS 320 -- Library Microform Facilities (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - LS 320 -- Gleaves, Edwin S., “A Microform Program for the Duckworth Libraries” (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - LIS 3200 -- Serials On-line Transparencies (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - LS 320 -- “WLB’s Miniguide to Microform for Library Users” (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - LIS 3200 -- OCLC (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - LS 320 -- Guide to Information about Microforms (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - LS 320 -- References and Reviews (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - LS 320 -- Micrographics Equipment Review (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - LS 320 -- Samples (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - LS 320 -- Videodisks (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - LS 320 -- Medical Serials in Microform (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - University Microforms International (Information on Serials Subscription) (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - LS 320 -- ERIC (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - LS 320 -- “Periodicals: Which Way to Keep Them?” 36 National Micrographics Association (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - LS 320 -- “Introduction to Micrographs” (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - LS 320 -- Supplementary Readings (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - LS 320 -- Serials in Microform (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - Selecting Microforms (Micrographic Association of Australia) (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - LIS 3200 -- Survey on Micrographics Education for Librarians (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - LIS 3200 -- Selected Readings (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - LIS 3200 -- “Micrographics” by Saffady & Gleaves (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - LIS 3200 -- “Microform Serials Acquisition” (ESG & RTC) (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - LIS 3200 -- Micrographics Resources for the Study of Microforms (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - LS 320 -- Revised Criteria for the Procurement and Use of Microforms and Related Equipment (Box 5, Folder 46)
  - LIS 3200 -- Micrographics in Libraries, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 47)
  - LS 320 -- Introduction to Micrographics (English & Spanish) (Box 5, Folder 48)
  - LIS 3200 -- ARL Microform Cataloging Clearinghouse (Box 5, Folder 49)
  - LS 320 -- Cataloging and Classification (Box 5, Folder 50)
  - LIS 3200 -- Text for Slide Presentation (Box 5, Folder 51)
  - LS 320 -- Articles (Box 5, Folder 52)
  - MLS -- Fall, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 53)
  - LS 320 -- Library Materials in Microform -- General Materials (Box 5, Folder 54)
  - LIS 3200 -- Films (Box 5, Folder 55)
  - LS 320 -- Serials in Microform -- Subscription Service (Box 5, Folder 56)
  - LIS 3200 -- Selecting Microforms (MAA) (Box 5, Folder 57)
  - LIS 3200 -- Microbook Library Series (Box 5, Folder 58)
  - Micrographics (Box 5, Folder 59)
  - LS 320 -- Articles (Box 5, Folder 60)
- LS 320, MICROGRAPHICS
  - LS 320 -- Evaluation of Module on Microforms (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - LS 320 -- Computer Output Microfilm (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - LS 320 -- SDC and Lockheed (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - LS 320 -- Originals (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - LS 320 -- NMA (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - LS 320 -- Off Campus / Originals (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Microforms -- Reviews (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Microforms -- Correspondence, Letters of Micropublishers (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Microforms -- Selected Reading List on Microforms (Original LS Copy) (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - LS 320 -- National Microfilm Library (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - LS 320 -- Microform Workshops and Conference (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - ERIC -- RCU -- Computer Search (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - LS 320 -- Effective Microform Environment (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - LS 320 -- Reading Assignments (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - LS 320 -- ERIC Exercises (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - LS 320 -- Special Materials (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - LS 320 -- Letters to Micropublishers, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - LS 320 -- VA Proposal (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - LS 320 -- “What Is Microfilm? (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - LS 320 -- Misc. Materials (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - LS 320 -- “A Selective Bibliography on Microforms, 1970-75” (Original) (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - LS 320 -- Preservation on Microform (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - LS 320/221 -- Microforms -- Some Basic References Compiled by USIA (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - LS 320 -- Peabody-in-Memphis (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - LS 320 -- (Memphis) -- Supplementary Readings (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - LS 320 -- Microform Materials -- Peabody-in-Memphis (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - LS 320 -- Examinations (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - LS 320 -- El Medio Invisible (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Microformatos -Materials (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - LS 320 -- “Creacion de un Ambiente” (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Los Microformatos -- Universidad de Guanajuato, Julio, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - El Medio Invisible, Marzo, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Problemas en la Applicacion de los Microformatos (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Ventajas de la Microfotografia en las Bibliotecas (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - LS 320 -- Materiales en Espanial (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - LS 320 -- “La Era de Microfilm” (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - LS 320 -- Equipment -- Camaras (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - Los Microformatos -- ERIC (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - LIS 3200 -- Los Microformatos: Programa de Estudio (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - LS 320 -- Spanish Materials (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - LS 320 -- “Calculos Papa el Costo.. .” (Box 6, Folder 41)
- LIS 3210, SERIAL PUBLICATIONS LS 302, ACADEMIC LIBRARY ADMINISTRATION WRITINGS AND REPORTS, 1954-1967
  - LIS 3210 -- Course of Study (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - LIS 3210 -- Related Readings (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - LIS 3210 -- Working with Serials Selection Tools (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - LIS 3210 -- Bibliography (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - LIS 3210 -- Unit 5 -- Handouts (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - LIS 3210 -- Unit 6 -- Handouts (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - LIS 3210 -- Selection Tools (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - LIS 3210 -- Special Bibliographical Note (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - LIS 3210 -- Serial Publication OCLC CED-ROM Search of CIJE Database, Sample Formats (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - LIS 3210 -- Serial Publication SERIALS & LIBRARIES: A BIB BASED UPON THE OCLC CD-ROM (1) (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - LIS 3210 -- Serial Publication SERIALS & LIBRARIES: A BIB BASED UPON THE OCLC CD-ROM (2) (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - LIS 3210 -- Serials, Records and Claims (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - LIS 3210 -- Citation and Use Studies (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - LIS 3210 -- Magazine Logos (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - LIS 3210 -- Serial Publications -- SERIALS LIBRARIAN Job Description (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - LIS 3210 -- Serial Publications -- Discussion Questions (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - LIS 3210 -- Exercises and Assignments (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - LIS 3210 -- Notebook (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - LIS 2210/3210 -- University of Tennessee at Martin (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - LIS 2210/3210 -- Mercy College (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - LIS 3210 -- Serials Publications -- Little magazines (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - LIS 3210 -- Serials Publications -- Tabloids (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - LIS 3210 -- Serials Publications -- Newspapers (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - LIS 3210 -- Selected Readings from THE SERIALS LIBRARIAN (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - LIS 3210 -- Faxon Company (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - LIS 3210 -- CIJE Bibliography (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - LIS 3210 -- Unit I -- Handouts (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - LIS 3210 -- Serials Publications -- Mercy College Libraries Periodicals Manual (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - LIS 3210 -- Leading U.S. Magazines (TR) (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - LIS 3210 --DLC (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - LIS 3210 -- UBE News in, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - LIS 3210 -- Managing the Serials Explosion (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - LIS 3210 -- Serials Publications -- Examination E (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - LIS 3210 -- Review for Quiz (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - LIS 3210 -- Notes (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - LIS 3210 -- History of Magazines (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - LIS 3210 -- Serials Publications -- Mercy College Libraries (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - LIS 3210 -- Case Studies -- Spring, 1894 (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - LIS 3210 -- OCLC (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - LIS 3210 -- Transparencies (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - LIS 3210 -- Fulfillment Houses (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - LIS 3210 -- On-line Serial Services EBSCO AND FAXON (Box 7, Folder 42)
  - LS 302 -- “Guidelines for Two-Year College Learning Resources Programs” (Box 7, Folder 43)
  - LS 302 -- Assignments (Box 7, Folder 44)
  - LS 302 -- Class Calendar (Box 7, Folder 45)
  - LS 302 -- Community/Junior College Library/Learning Resources Centers --A Preliminary Bibliography (Box 7, Folder 46)
  - LS 302 -- Correspondence (Box 7, Folder 47)
  - LS 302 -- Course of Study (Box 7, Folder 48)
  - LS 302 -- Examinations (Box 7, Folder 49)
  - LS 302 -- Carnegie Commission Reports (Box 7, Folder 50)
  - LS 302 -- Draft; Guidelines for Branch Libraries in Colleges and Universities (Box 7, Folder 51)
  - LS 302 -- Related Materials (Box 7, Folder 52)
  - LS 302 -- (Jackson) Higher Education -- Bibliography (Box 7, Folder 53)
  - LS 302 -- “Standards for Faculty States for College and University Libraries” (Box 7, Folder 54)
  - LS 302 --(Jackson) Reading and Reference List (Box 7, Folder 55)
  - LS 302 -- Statistical Summary of Joint University Libraries, 1936/37 to 1972/73 (Box 7, Folder 56)
  - LS 302 -- Academic Administration -- Larry Bone Summer 1976, Term 1 (Box 7, Folder 57)
  - Conrad -- The Nigger of the “Narcissus” (Box 7, Folder 58)
  - “Hemingway and Baroja... “ (Box 7, Folder 59)
  - Hemingway -- “On the Spanish Trail of E. H.” (Box 7, Folder 60)
  - Housman, “Loveliest of Trees” (Box 7, Folder 61)
  - “Going Fishing in the Sky” (ESG) (Box 7, Folder 62)
  - “Growing Up Without Giving Up” (Box 7, Folder 63)
  - “Guide to the... Reference Resources” (Box 7, Folder 64)
  - Howells, W. D. -- INDIAN SUMMER (Box 7, Folder 65)
  - Ibsen, Henrik -- Criticism (Box 7, Folder 66)
  - Leavis, F. R. -- The Great Tradition (Review) (Box 7, Folder 67)
  - “Literature and the Ministry” (Box 7, Folder 68)
  - “Point of Views in the Nigger of the Narcissus” -- A New Reading (ESG) (Box 7, Folder 69)
  - Synge, J. M. -- Deirdre of the Sorrows (Box 7, Folder 70)
  - Thoreau (Freshman Research Paper) (Box 7, Folder 71)
  - Thoreau -- “Walking” (Box 7, Folder 72)
  - “The Thin Crooked Line” (ESG) (Box 7, Folder 73)
- LS 307/LIS 3070, LITERARY RESEARCH AND BIBLIOGRAPHY LIS 3710, LATIN AMERICAN SEMINAR LS 320/3200, MICROGRAPHICS LS/ED 260A, INTRODUCTION TO MEDIA STUDIES
  - LS 320 -- MCA -- Youth, Law and Justice (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - LS 320 -- SPEC & OMS .Duplicate packet from Microform Collections -- kit 59 (Box 8, Folder 2)